{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124868190","data":{"timestamp":" 947124868189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fulana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124869204","data":{"timestamp":" 947124869203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fulana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124870079","data":{"timestamp":" 947124870078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fulana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124873661","data":{"timestamp":" 947124873660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124874050","data":{"timestamp":" 947124874049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124874342","data":{"timestamp":" 947124874341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" no"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124878750","data":{"timestamp":" 947124878749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124879156","data":{"timestamp":" 947124879156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nga"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124879482","data":{"timestamp":" 947124879480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124884212","data":{"timestamp":" 947124884212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kofia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124884586","data":{"timestamp":" 947124884586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kofia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fi"," userResponse":" fi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124884936","data":{"timestamp":" 947124884936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kofia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124889226","data":{"timestamp":" 947124889226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124889867","data":{"timestamp":" 947124889867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124890317","data":{"timestamp":" 947124890316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124913648","data":{"timestamp":" 947124913648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124914048","data":{"timestamp":" 947124914047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124920954","data":{"timestamp":" 947124920953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124921552","data":{"timestamp":" 947124921552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124930241","data":{"timestamp":" 947124930241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124930666","data":{"timestamp":" 947124930665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124931017","data":{"timestamp":" 947124931016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124936073","data":{"timestamp":" 947124936073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ofisi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124936479","data":{"timestamp":" 947124936478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ofisi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fi"," userResponse":" fi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124936804","data":{"timestamp":" 947124936803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ofisi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124941203","data":{"timestamp":" 947124941202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124941602","data":{"timestamp":" 947124941602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124941902","data":{"timestamp":" 947124941902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124954255","data":{"timestamp":" 947124954254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_simama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124954570","data":{"timestamp":" 947124954570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_simama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124954962","data":{"timestamp":" 947124954961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_simama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124957641","data":{"timestamp":" 947124957638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 429d4e54-8f0e-457c-b844-e68809fc6a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_simama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124969162","data":{"timestamp":" 947124969161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124969395","data":{"timestamp":" 947124969395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124970371","data":{"timestamp":" 947124970370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124971659","data":{"timestamp":" 947124971658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124974680","data":{"timestamp":" 947124974679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124975534","data":{"timestamp":" 947124975533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124975855","data":{"timestamp":" 947124975854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124977098","data":{"timestamp":" 947124977097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124980755","data":{"timestamp":" 947124980754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124981750","data":{"timestamp":" 947124981750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124982014","data":{"timestamp":" 947124982014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124982971","data":{"timestamp":" 947124982970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124985978","data":{"timestamp":" 947124985977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124987022","data":{"timestamp":" 947124987021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124987502","data":{"timestamp":" 947124987502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124992125","data":{"timestamp":" 947124992123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947124992415","data":{"timestamp":" 947124992414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" 30bf118f-cbbe-41f8-978f-9605c3160731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947125015893","data":{"timestamp":" 947125015893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" cc00274f-851d-4839-91d8-94acc3a603d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947125020547","data":{"timestamp":" 947125020546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" cc00274f-851d-4839-91d8-94acc3a603d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947125023659","data":{"timestamp":" 947125023658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" cc00274f-851d-4839-91d8-94acc3a603d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947125023968","data":{"timestamp":" 947125023967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_051343"," gameId":" cc00274f-851d-4839-91d8-94acc3a603d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}